{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1. This is a Sample Question 1?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "2. This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
      
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "3. This is a Sample Question 3?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "4. This is a Sample Question 4?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. This is a Sample Question 5?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "6. This is a Sample Question 6?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "7. This is a Sample Question 7?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "8. This is a Sample Question 8?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "9. This is a Sample Question 9?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "10. This is a Sample Question 10?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
    
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
  ]
}
